<resources xmlns:name="http://schemas.android.com/tools">


    <string name="group_goal">Our goal is to showcase each of our members as accomplished and capable individuals, and to elevate our identities as a team.</string>

    <string name="app_name">Team CLDS</string>

    <string name="bio_danny">I am an artist from Queens, passionate about all forms of art who is currently working to fuse my interests in tech and design into a viable and successful career.</string>


    <string name="bio_caroline">Caroline hails from Flushing, and is a garlic fiend to no one’s surprise.
        There’s a reason why she’s always chewing gum. She expects to live until she’s 101 as a spritely elderly lady.
        And in between, build some unforgettable codes - both insanely good and terribly bad.
    </string>

    <string name="bio_linda">Linda is 28 years old, fluent in Spanish and English and a mother
        of two.  She recently got engaged,had her second daughter, and got accepted into this coding program (2018 has been
        a great year!).  On her down time she enjoys watching Netflix, going to Target, and making Starbucks runs (Vanilla chai
        all day).  In the future, she hopes to have a lucrative career with the opportunities to move from
        her home on Long Island to a place with a much warmer climate year round.
    </string>

    <string name="bio_sanje">Born in Nepal and currently residing in Queens with my family.
        I am many things to many people, but I am most proud to be a good son and a loving brother.
    </string>

    <string name="PathFinder_Linda_Link">Pathfinder</string>
    <string name="HauntedHouse_Linda_Link">Haunted House</string>
    <string name="MadLibs_Linda_Link">MadLibs</string>

    <string name="drawer_item_caroline">Caroline</string>
    <string name="drawer_item_linda">Linda</string>
    <string name="drawer_item_danny">Danny</string>
    <string name="drawer_item_sanje">Sanje</string>

    <string name="linkedin_caroline">https://www.linkedin.com/in/carolinehkang/</string>
    <string name="linkedin_danny">https://www.linkedin.com/in/hyunki-chung/</string>
    <string name="Linkedin_sanje">https://www.linkedin.com/in/sanje-lama-038158134/</string>
    <string name="linkedin_linda">https://www.linkedin.com/in/LindaPokorny</string>


</resources>
